ssavr.com 2019-05-26

# Privacy Policy | Simple.Savr

##### Like Simple.Savr?

##### Quick Links

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us. [Click here to contact us.](https://www.ssavr.com/contact)

We consider the privacy of our visitors and users to be extremely important. This privacy policy describes in detail the types of personal information is collected and recorded by us and how we use it. 

### Log Files

Like many other Web sites, we make use of log files. These files merely logs visitors to the site - usually a standard procedure for hosting companies and a part of hosting services' analytics. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet Service Provider (ISP), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages and user agent. This information is used to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable. 

### Information You Provide

By using Simple.Savr, you understand that we do not have any text you typed saved in plain copy saved in database. It is encrypted using the encryption text provided by you. If no encryption text was provided, it is encrypted using the default encryption text which is randomly generated. Any information typed in the text is instantly saved in database (and is encrypted) and deleted instantly as soon as it is removed from the text box. We log the text using IP addresses so that we can display them to all of your devices. The text you type in the text box is not, in any form or method, shared with anyone. 

We also allow you to upload files to our service that is automatically synced to all your added IPs. Your uploaded files are stored on our servers which can be deleted by anyone who is under your added IP address. This action can be protected by setting up a password. Your uploaded files are automatically deleted every 7 days to protect your files. 

In addition to uploading files, you are also able to compress and download all your uploaded files at once for convenience. The compressed file is automatically deleted after it has been downloaded. If our server is under heavy load and the compressed file is not deleted immediately after being downloaded, it will be automatically deleted before within 24 hours as a result of daily server cleanups. 

You have the ability to set a password for your savr, which prevents anyone else from viewing your savr without the correct password. Your savr will not be decrypted without the password, if password is enabled. If no password is enabled, you understand that anyone who is under your IP address is able to view and edit your savr. 

We give you an option to add and link multiple IP Addresses so that multiple IPs can view, create, edit and delete your savr, in addition to upload, download and delete files. If you have added additional IPs to your IP, you understand that anyone who is under the added IP can edit, view, delete your savr and uploaded files. 

### Destroy Information

Unlike other services, we allow you to destroy and permanently [delete](https://www.ssavr.com/debug) all information that we have stored about you, which includes your IP address, savr, uploaded files, user agent and referring/exit pages. After your delete your information, it will be deleted instantly from our servers. However, our backup system may still have your information which will be automatically deleted within 60 days. 

### Cookies and Web Beacons

We use cookies to store information about our visitor's preferences, to record user-specific information on which pages the site visitor accesses or visits, and to personalize or customize our web page content based upon visitors' browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser. 

### Our Advertising Partners

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partner is Google. You may consult this listing to find the privacy policy for each of our advertising partners by contacting us. These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology in their respective advertisements and links that appear on our site and which are sent directly to your browser. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons) may also be used by our site's third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertising campaigns and/or to personalize the advertising content that you see on the site. 

We have no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers. You, however, have the ability to disable ads on this site from your settings which will cut all communication with our advertising partner. 

### Third Party Privacy Policies

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. Our privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites. 

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers' respective websites. 

### Children's Information

We believe it is important to provide added protection for children online. We encourage parents and guardians to spend time online with their children to observe, participate in and/or monitor and guide their online activity. We do not knowingly collect any personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13. If a parent or guardian believes that hwe have, in our database, the personally-identifiable information of a child under the age of 13, please [contact](https://www.ssavr.com/contact) us immediately and we will use our best efforts to promptly remove such information from our records. Alternatively, you may delete all information that we about you or your children by [clicking here.](https://www.ssavr.com/debug)

### Consent

By using Simple.Savr, you hereby consent to our privacy policy and agree to its terms. 

### Update 

This Privacy Policy was last updated on: Friday, December 9th, 2016.   
_Should we update, amend or make any changes to our privacy policy, those changes will be posted here._
